scifiscoop.com 2013-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Sci Fi Scoop

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Statement

At our site, the privacy of our visitors is of high importance to us. This privacy policy explains the type of personal information received and collected by this site and how it may be used.

### Log Files

Just like many other websites, our site makes use of log files. The information contained in those log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We have no access to or control over cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This sites privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you want to to disable cookies, you can do this through your individual browser options. You will find more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers at the browsers’ respective websites.
